EPISODE 2: PRISONER FE40536: JOLYNE CUJOH
Welcome, inmates.
I am the warden of
Green Dolphin Street State Prison,
Locobaroco.
And this lovely crocodile here
is Charlotte, my assistant.
Great to meet you!
Charlotte,
please explain how life is
in this institution.
Okay!
Similar to the United States,
this prison is based on
the concept of freedom and equality.
You may freely walk around the facility
and exercise as you please.
You may use the phones,
the shower, and the library as well.
If you are an exemplary inmate,
you may even own a TV.
You could also work or study
and earn university credits.
That's right.
Yes! What is it, Charlotte?
But Warden, there are rules too, right?
You're absolutely correct, Charlotte!
First, do not remove the wristband
with your inmate number.
No lending or borrowing of items
between inmates.
No possession of metal objects.
How about earrings?
The warden's still speaking! Shut up!
Earrings are prohibited,
FE40536, Jolyne Cujoh.
Feel free to ask any questions
to the prison guards.
You are now dismissed.
All right! Everyone, face left!
It's so spacious.
The entire island is the prison.
Oh, a crocodile.
FE40536.
Cell 206 will be your home from now on.
Today's free time is over.
The cells open at 6:30 a.m.
Breakfast begins at seven,
but you may choose to sleep in.
Try to get along now.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
I'm Jolyne.
I'm Gwess.
Want some?
Thanks.
But I don't have an appetite.
There's so much to get used to--
Ouch! What the hell--
The bottom bunk is mine!
You got a problem with that, you bitch?
I didn't mean to instigate a fight.
I just misunderstood since
your things were on the top bunk.
That charm!
Bitch!
Get your dirty hands off of my stuff!
Can I see that charm?
There should be a small stone
and a photograph of my parents inside!
It could have belonged to me!
I bought it for two dollars
from a newcomer the other day.
Because it's just so beautiful.
Let me see it!
You better watch your mouth, ugly!
Okay, I'll buy it off of you.
How much do you want?
Two hundred dollars.
What?
You heard me, dumbass. I said 200 dollars.
You bitch…
Lights out!
What's going on?
Too much is happening all at once.
I have so much to think about.
I'm so sad that I'm starting to cry.
What the hell?
I'm sorry. About last night, I mean.
What?
It's morning.
Here.
You can look at it.
But…
There was nothing inside it.
No pictures, no nothing.
See?
Was there anything else in it?
Like a stone?
No. Nothing.
Anyway, please forgive
my behavior last night.
I'm shy around new people.
Oh, there's nothing to forgive.
It was my fault.
I don't know the rules around here yet.
Jolyne, you are a good person.
Let's be friends from now on.
Yes, I'd like that.
Anyway, it's breakfast time.
I'll see you there.
Hold on, I'll go with you.
What the hell?
There's water all over the place!
My pants are soaking wet. This sucks!
What do you mean it's "sold out"?
I haven't eaten yet.
As you can see,
you're free to sleep in.
You're also free to get here late.
Isn't there food for everyone?
Any leftover milk or bananas?
That's the strange thing about prisons.
That makes no sense!
Oh, Jolyne, you took your sweet time.
I'm so full.
Hey, Gwess.
You had two milk cartons and two bananas!
Two bananas?
No way. Are you still asleep?
Also, sorry about the water.
I accidentally spilled it.
I'll clean it up later.
I already cleaned it off.
Oh, thank you.
You're so kind, Jolyne.
This is…
Jump for me. I believe in you.
I love you,
and you love me.
Don't we trust one another?
Do it for me.
Good boy!
Aren't you an adorable little birdie?
Good job! Here's your reward!
Good morning!
No, Pi-chan.
Not "good morning."
Say "I love you."
You're such a darling
when you say that you love me.
I love you!
Good boy!
You're such a good boy, Pi-chan!
Next, perch.
Jump over.
Taking risks is part
of trust-building, Pi-chan.
What?
Come on, jump!
Whoa…
What did you just say? "Whoa"?
Say that again!
Do birds go "whoa"?
I love you! I love you! I love you!
You're covering it up now, aren't you?
You think such a blatant lie works on me?
Do you?
I've had it with you.
We're through.
What was that?
A banana?
What is this?
Though it's tiny,
it's definitely real.
That woman…
had already killed it!
What is she doing?
I knew it, she must have used that charm
to gain some sort of ability!
Where did she get that tiny human?
What…
happened to me?
STAND NAME: G.G. DOLLS
STAND MASTER: GWESS
This is…
My body shrank!
I knew it was you.
How did you snatch away my Pi-chan?
Jolyne!
Jolyne.
I'm starting to like you, really.
What happened to my body?
Explain!
Listen, Jolyne. Please don't talk.
The person inside that parrot--
Hey, I said no talking!
Get in it.
I removed its guts.
There was a flaw to using a parrot.
Birds can't use their arms
and they can't grab.
Rats, though, have front paws.
He was a prison guard
who got fired for slacking off.
The warden thinks he left the facility.
Also, I told you to keep quiet.
But if you can mimic
a rat squeak, I'll let it pass.
You can say, "I'm going, squeak!"
or "I'm hungry, squeak!"
Got it?
Just as I thought, you look darling!
Now it's time for training.
Go, faster. Run!
No slowing down.
Lift, Chorokichi.
Chorokichi?
Everything has a name.
The Word was with God,
and all things were created by the Word.
That's why I named this power
that shrank your size.
"G.G. Dolls."
This is the name of my mental power.
Let's stack another book.
You…
You think you can cheat me like that?
How dare you betray my trust.
We're through!
Just kidding!
You passed, Chorokichi.
Your shrewdness will prove useful.
Very very good!
Can you see?
Down this corridor is the control room.
The switch within that room
can deactivate the locks in this facility.
You can pass through.
You see what I'm getting at.
You are I are breaking out.
For some reason, I can't shrink myself.
But if we cooperate, we can leave.
We need to trust each other.
Of course, we'll need
to concoct a more reliable plan.
First, I want you to check out
everything beyond this corridor.
Do you really think we can escape?
I told you to squeak like a rat!
Squeak, how do I get
to the control room, squeak?
How cute! How precious.
But how should I know, dumbass?
That's why you're on this mission.
Look up.
That's the surveillance camera.
But it can't see below this bar.
Walk under the handrail.
Put your hood on.
Now go!
Hey, you. What are you doing?
That's right, you with the headband.
State your name and number!
FE18081.
My name is Gwess.
I'm just loitering around.
If you have no business here, then leave!
Leave immediately.
Sure thing, Mr. Prison Guard.
There are four steel doors.
Which one is the control room?
Also, there are two cameras here.
What's going on? I'm running out of space.
What's happening?
Did you hear that?
Yes, I heard it too.
It was close by.
My body…
It's getting larger!
The coffee's ready.
Maybe it was from the coffee maker.
-It didn't sound like it.
-This is bad. What's going on?
Distance?
Is it because Gwess is far from me?
Is this ability affected by distance?
I heard it again!
Something's lurking nearby!
Shit!
It's right under there!
Hey, move out of the way!
I said move it!
That's hot!
What the hell, man?
What the…
I told you it was from the coffee maker!
My bad.
This investigation is over!
I need to get back before I get too big!
What is that?
G.G. Dolls!
This monster…
It resembles a doll, but it's transparent.
It's just like my thread.
Others can't see it.
It's the materialization
of Gwess's ability.
"G.G. Dolls."
This is the name of my mental power.
It shrank me
and tore the prison guard to shreds!
This shithead was inside the rat with me!
And Gwess.
She didn't know that
the ability would get deactivated.
My body is returning to its original size.
This monster thinks I'm ditching,
so he's here for a hunt!
Not only that,
he wants to completely kill me!
-G.G. Dolls!
-Shit!
Why is this happening to me?
Am I going to get killed
by a monster like him?
I'm stuck!
Threads.
A bundle of threads.
This must be the shape of my energy.
Its form!
The yarn weaves into its form.
Hey, monster!
Scream, you shithead!
Get Gwess.
Hurry!
Jolyne…
Turns out you have an ability.
Gwess!
Stop!
Don't hurt my precious G.G. Dolls!
Shut up!
Make my body smaller so I can escape!
Just by a bit, though, got it?
All right, you can sleep on
the bottom bunk bed!
Please don't hate me despite
what happened between us!
But please squeak every once in a while.
Just hurry it up!
Finally.
Now, the charm.
Give me the stone
and tell me who sold it to you.
Of course.
Two hundred dollars, was it--
Shut up, bitch!
Tell me who sold it to you!
All right.
Some woman named Ermes sold it to me.
Ermes?
I don't know much about her.
Here.
Well…
I got her!
Guards! We have a problem!
This bitch here crossed the gun point!
Come here, quick!
What are you doing there?
How did you get over there?
Jailbreak!
Code 999!
It's all over for you now.
The prison guard
is retrieving the shotgun as we speak.
He has every right to shoot you down!
No questions asked!
Jolyne!
Serves you right!
It's what you get
for trampling on my heart!
Good grief, Gwess.
You said everything has a name.
I'll name this ability of mine too.
"Stone Ocean."
I'll become free
from this ocean of stones.
Did you hear me?
Stone Ocean. That's the name.
If there's a hierarchy system
in this prison, I'll follow it.
However, I'm the one who gives orders.
Now let me cross over.
-What?
-Where is she?
-She disappeared.
-What?
Are you sure she was there?
Well, I just saw her back, so…
Strange…
Dad…
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter